xtb.com 2015-03-17

# XTB Privacy Policy

XTB Privacy Policy
The purpose of this privacy policy is to provide you, with details of how X Open Hub Ltd (“XTB UK”
“we” or “us”) will collect and use the information you supply to us, including where applicable any
personal data.
Please read this privacy policy carefully. It is the stated policy of XTB that we will act in accordance
with current legislation and aim to meet current best practice with regard to the processing of
personal data.
We understand the importance of maintaining the privacy of your personal information. By
entrusting us with your information, we would like to assure you of our commitment to keeping it
private. We have taken measurable steps to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of your
information.
If you decide to apply to open an account with us, there is certain information that we will require
from you in order to do so. This information includes, but is not limited to personal details such as
name, address, date of birth, contact details, employment details, assets and liabilities, payment
details, including credit card, debit card and bank account details, and other necessary financial
information. From time to time we may also request further information to help us improve our
service to you. We obtain most of the information directly from you through application or other
forms, and from maintaining records of information provided in the course of ongoing customer
service. We may also collect information about your use of the website, such as pages visited,
frequency and duration and visit and trading activities.
We will use information collected from you to provide the information and services requested by you
and to improve the quality of our service. Unless you are informed otherwise, the personal
information we hold is used for establishing and managing your account, reviewing your ongoing
needs, enhancing customer service and products, giving you ongoing information or opportunities
that we believe may be relevant to you.
We limit access of your data to only those employees or partners that need to know the information
in order to assist in carrying out your request for products or services. We have procedures in place
regarding how to safeguard and use non public personal information.
Depending on the product or service concerned and particular restrictions on sensitive information,
this means that personal information may be disclosed to: service providers and specialist advisers to
us who have been contracted to provide us with administrative, financial, research or other services;
referring parties and introducing partners with whom we have a mutual relationship; courts, tribunals
and regulatory authorities as agreed or authorised by the law, and when we believe that disclosure is
necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding; or reference agencies;
anyone authorised by an individual, as specified by that individual or the contract.
The following measures are in place to safeguard your personal data:
          Access to your account is controlled by password and username which are unique to you
          Your personal data is stored on secure servers
          Payment details are encrypted using Ingrain devices which provide tamper-resistant
           protection of cryptographic keys to ensure encrypted data is kept private and secure.
While we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal data, you acknowledge that the
use of the internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or
integrity of any personal data transferred from you, or to you via the internet.
 XTB UK is a trading name of X Open Hub Limited. X Open Hub Limited is authorised and regulated by the UK Financial Conduct
    Authority (FRN522157) with its registered and trading office at 7th Floor, 29 Marylebone Road, London NW1 5JX, United
                                            Kingdom (company number 07227848).
                                                                                                                    v. 030714

We will not keep information for any longer than is required. In many cases, personal information
must be kept for considerable periods of time. Retention periods will be determined taking into
account the type of personal information that is collected and the purpose for which it is collected,
bearing in mind the requirements applicable to the situation and the need to destroy outdated,
unused information at the earliest reasonable time.
You may inform us at any time that your personal details have changed or that you wish us to delete
personal information we hold about you by emailing us at ukservice@xtb.com. We will change or
delete your personal information in accordance with your instructions, except to the extent that we
are required to hold your personal information for regulatory or legal purposes, to provide you with
the services you have requested or to maintain adequate business records.
If you open an account with us, you will need to use our trading software which enables us to use
cookies in relation to your access to this website.
Cookies are small files of information, which often include a unique identification number or value,
which are stored on your computer’s hard drive as a result of you using this trading software and
accessing this website. The purpose of this information is to provide you with a more relevant and
effective experience on this website, including presenting web pages according to your needs or
preferences. Cookies are frequently used on many websites on the internet and you can choose if and
how a cookie will be accepted by changing your preferences and options in your browser. You may
not be able to access some parts of this site if you choose to disable the cookie acceptance in your
browser, particularly the secure parts of the website. We therefore recommend you enable cookie
acceptance to benefit from all the services on the website.
Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to, or
control over, these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only and
does not cover the use of cookies by any third party.
Our website contains links to websites operated by other parties. We provide the links for your
convenience, but we do not review, control or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by
others, and this privacy policy does not apply to such third party websites. We are not responsible for
the performance of websites operated by third parties or for you business dealings with them.
Under the Data Protection Act, you have the right to obtain a copy of any personal information which
we hold about you and to advise us of any perceived inaccuracy. The Act does set out some
exceptions to this.
To make a request, please contact us, verifying your identity and specifying what information you
require. We may charge a fee.
You may contact us via e-mail compliance@xtb.co.uk or write to us at XTB UK Limited 29 Marylebone
Road, London NW1 5JX.
From time to time, we may update this Privacy Statement. In the event we materially change this
Privacy Statement, the revised Privacy Statement will promptly be posted to the websites and we will
post a notice on our websites informing you of such changes. You agree to accept posting of a revised
Privacy Statement electronically on the website as actual notice to you. Any dispute over our Privacy
Statement is subject to this notice and our Customer Agreement. We encourage you to periodically
check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we
use it, and to whom we disclose it.
If you have any questions regarding this policy, wish to access or change your information or have a
complaint, or if you have any questions about security on our Website, you may email us at
compliance@xtb.co.uk.
 XTB UK is a trading name of X Open Hub Limited. X Open Hub Limited is authorised and regulated by the UK Financial Conduct
    Authority (FRN522157) with its registered and trading office at 7th Floor, 29 Marylebone Road, London NW1 5JX, United
                                            Kingdom (company number 07227848).
                                                                                                                    v. 030714
